Miguel Diaz

969 159 564 | Manila Philippines

SUMMARY

I am senior full stack & blockchain developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. I have 4 years of blockchain development experience and 6 years of professional experience in Frontend and backend development. I have an important ability to work well in a team environment and good experience in project version control such as SVN, Git, Gitlab, Bitbucket.

EXPERIENCE:

Full Stack & Blockchain Developer / BuildFire (Manila, Philippines)

07/2019 - 03/2023

- Web applications, and programs based on Bitcoin and Ethereum with tracking and usage of cryptocurrencies...
- Developed blockchain services such as block explorer and web/mobile wallet. •
- Working knowledge of crypto/blockchain trading systems for DEX and NFT games.
- Developed ERC20, ERC721 token contracts and deployed on BSC and Polygon.
- Developed smart contracts for NFT marketplace, Staking Pool, Yield Farming,
- Created subgraph, Rest Apis for token prices and user data.

Full Stack Developer / Webcreek (Manila, Philippines)

08/2017 - 04/2019

- Development web application and mobile apps with senior developers
- Developed various websites using MERN and MEVN stack.
- Experience with many mobile app development such as Poker, Casino, Game, Taxi app, delivery app, social app, dating app, etc.
- Developed tons of mobile apps using React Native

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree: Computer Science 06/2013 - 06/2017

Nanyang Technological of University – Singapo

SKILLS

Back End & Server

- Node.js | Express | PHP | Laravel | Django
- · mysql | mssql | mongodb | postgreSQL | Firebase
- · git | svn
- . Asana | Trello | Jira
- · EC2 | AWS | S3

Front End

- · React.js | Next.js | Vue.js | Angular.js | Ember.js
- · HTML | CSS | BootStrap | Tailwind CSS | JavaScript | TypeScript

Blockchain

- · Ethereum | Binance Smart Chain | Polygon | Avalanche
- · NFT Marketplace | DEX | CEX | BlockExplorer
- · Web3.js | Ether.js |
- . Solidity | Vyper

Other

- . C/C++ | C# | Java
- . Unity3D | C# | Javascript
- . openCV | openGL